[{"question": "A judge's private room, without the press or the public being present","answer" : "In  camera"},
{"question": "A period of time in the past that was idyllically happy and peaceful","answer" : "Halcyon"},
{"question": "A tax or levy","answer" : "Cess"},
{"question": "An abbreviation formed from the initial letters of other words and pronounced  as a word","answer" : "Acronym"},
{"question": "An ability to do several things at the same time","answer" : "Multitasking"},
{"question": "An ability to express oneself well in speech","answer" : "Oracy"},
{"question": "An ability to make good judgements and take quick decisions","answer" : "Acumen"},
{"question": "An ability to see what will or might happen in the","answer" : "Foresight"},
{"question": "An ability to stay calm in difficult or dangerous situations","answer" : "Sangfroid"},
{"question": "An ability to use one's hands skillfully or an ability to think quickly and  effectively","answer" : "Dexterity"},
{"question": "An ability, talent, or special skill needed to do something","answer" : "Knack"},
{"question": "Able to become strong, healthy, or successful again after something bad  happens","answer" : "Resilient"},
{"question": "Able to do many different things","answer" : "Versatile"},
{"question": "Able to exist together without trouble or conflict going together well","answer" : " Compatible"},
{"question": "Acceptable according to the law, fair or reasonable","answer" : "Valid"},
{"question": "Accepting and closely following the traditional beliefs and customs of a  religion","answer" : "Orthodox"},
{"question": "An act of burying a dead person","answer" : "Interment"},
{"question": "An act of carefully watching someone or something especially in order to  prevent or detect a crime","answer" : "Surveillance"},
{"question": "An act of causing two people or groups to become friendly again after an  argument or disagreement","answer" : "Reconciliation"},
{"question": "An act of committing a serious crime such as murder or rape","answer" : "Felony"},
{"question": "An act of destroying or damaging something deliberately so that it does not  work correctly","answer" : "Sabotage"},
{"question": "An act of ending the employment of a worker or group of workers","answer" : "Layoff"},
{"question": "An act of explaining something","answer" : "Exposition"},
{"question": "An act of getting money back from people it has been paid to","answer" : "Clawback"},
{"question": "An act of going or travelling to a place along a way that is different from the  usual or planned way","answer" : "Detour"},
{"question": "An act of identifying a disease, illness, or problem by examining someone or  something","answer" : "Diagnosis"},
{"question": "An act of illegally copying someone's product or invention without permission ","answer" : "Piracy     "},
{"question": "An act of no longer caring for, using, or doing something, failure to do one's  job or duty","answer" : "Dereliction"},
{"question": "An act of officially charging someone with a crime","answer" : "Indictment"},
{"question": "An act of printing a statement about somebody that is not true and that gives  people a bad opinion of them","answer" : "Libel"},
{"question": "An act of punishing or harming somebody in return for what they have done to  you your family or friends","answer" : "Vengeance"},
{"question": "An act of remembering or telling about past experiences","answer" : "Reminiscence"},
{"question": "An act of returning something that was lost or stolen to its owner","answer" : "Restitution"},
{"question": "An act of sending someone to another person or place for treatment, help,  advice, etc.","answer" : "Referral"},
{"question": "An act of treating a holy place or object in a way that does not show proper  respect","answer" : "Sacrilege"},
{"question": "An act of trying to impress someone by saying the names of well-known people  that one knows or has met","answer" : "Name-dropping"},
{"question": "An act or fact of having a romantic or sexual relationship with someone other  than one's husband, wife, or partner","answer" : "Infidelity"},
{"question": "An act or means of sealing off a place to prevent goods or people from entering  or leaving","answer" : "Blockade"},
{"question": "An act or remark that is calculated to gain an advantage","answer" : "Gambit"},
{"question": "An act that is part of a usually religious ceremony","answer" : "Rite"},
{"question": "An act, activity, or process of finding the way to get to a place when one is  travelling in a ship, airplane, car","answer" : "Navigation"},
{"question": "An action of making amends for a wrong or injury","answer" : "Atonement"},
{"question": "An action of marrying a person of a superior caste or class","answer" : "Hypergamy"},
{"question": "An action of regaining or gaining possession of something in exchange for  payment, or clearing a debt","answer" : "Redemption"},
{"question": "An action or event that is a signal for somebody to do something","answer" : "Cue"},
{"question": "An action or offence of speaking sacrilegiously about God or sacred things;  profane talk","answer" : "Blasphemy"},
{"question": "An activity or art of copying the behavior or speech of other people","answer" : "Mimicry"},
{"question": "An activity or excitement that is unusual and that often is not wanted or  necessary","answer" : "Fuss"},
{"question": "An activity in that more and more people are becoming involved","answer" : "Bandwagon"},
{"question": "Actor or actress","answer" : "Thespian"},
{"question": "Add notes to (a text or diagram) giving explanation or comment","answer" : "Annotate"},
{"question": "An additional fact or piece of information about a story that occurs after the  main part","answer" : "Postscript"},
{"question": "Advantages or gains secured as a result of corrupt practices","answer" : "Graft"},
{"question": "An advice and future prediction based on the date of a person's birth and the  positions of the stars and planets","answer" : "Horoscope     "},
{"question": "Agreed to by everyone","answer" : "Unanimous"},
{"question": "An agreement between enemies or opponents to stop fighting, arguing, etc., for  a certain period of time","answer" : "Truce"},
{"question": "An alcoholic liquor especially when it is cheap or made illegally","answer" : "Hooch"},
{"question": "All the plants that live in a particular area, time, period, or environment","answer" : "Flora"},
{"question": "All the things that a person is able to do","answer" : "Repertoire"},
{"question": "Allowed to know about (something secret)","answer" : "Privy"},
{"question": "Always or often happening or existing","answer" : "Inveterate"},
{"question": "An amount (such as an amount of money) that is more than the amount that is  needed","answer" : "Surplus"},
{"question": "An amount of moneygiven to a retiring soldier or employee","answer" : "Gratuity"},
{"question": "An amount of money paid for a service","answer" : "Honorarium"},
{"question": "An amount of money that a company or the government pays to a person who  is old or sick and no longer works","answer" : "Pension"},
{"question": "An amount of money that is given to someone in return for providing help in a  secret and dishonest business deal","answer" : "Kickback"},
{"question": "An amount of money that is paid at one time","answer" : "Lump sum"},
{"question": "An amount of money that is spent","answer" : "Outlay"},
{"question": "An amount of money that must be paid and that is collected by a government or  other authority","answer" : "Levy"},
{"question": "An amount of something that is produced by a person or thing","answer" : "Output"},
{"question": "An amount of time that a person holds a job, office, or title","answer" : "Tenure"},
{"question": "Amusing and very strange","answer" : "Wacky"},
{"question": "An angry and unpleasant woman, sexually attractive woman","answer" : "Vixen"},
{"question": "An argument that is complicated and continues over a long period of time","answer" : " Wrangle"},
{"question": "An invigilator at a university or college examination","answer" : "Proctor"},
{"question": "An ancient text in the form of a book, official listof medicines or chemicals","answer" : " Codex"},
{"question": "Anger caused by something that is unfair or wrong","answer" : "Indignation"},
{"question": "An angry and usually long speech or piece of writing that strongly criticizes  someone or something","answer" : "Diatribe"},
{"question": "An angry woman who often complains about and criticizes other people","answer" : " Virago"},
{"question": "An animal or plant that lives in or on another animal or plant and gets food or  protection from it","answer" : "Parasite"},
{"question": "An animal that has four feet","answer" : "Quadruped"},
{"question": "Annoy (someone) by often complaining about his or her behavior, appearance","answer" : " Nag"},
{"question": "Annoyance or distress at having failed or been humiliated","answer" : "Chagrin     "},
{"question": "An annual calendar containing important dates and statistical information such  as astronomical data and tide tables","answer" : "Almanac"},
{"question": "Any one of the large parts that some countries are divided into","answer" : "Province"},
{"question": "Any one of the lines that go from the North Pole to the South Pole on maps of  the world","answer" : "Meridian"},
{"question": "Appearing, happening,, or arriving soon","answer" : "Forthcoming "},
{"question": "An area around or near a particular place","answer" : "Vicinity"},
{"question": "An area in a desert where there is water and plants","answer" : "Oasis"},
{"question": "An area of land that has a particular quality or appearance","answer" : "Landscape"},
{"question": "An area of sea water that is separated from the ocean by a reef or sandbar","answer" : " Lagoon"},
{"question": "An area of soft, wet ground; situation that is hard to deal with or get out of","answer" : " Quagmire"},
{"question": "An area that is not close to any cities or towns","answer" : "Hinterland"},
{"question": "An area with people who are different in some way from the people in the areas  around it","answer" : "Enclave"},
{"question": "An area within which someone or something has authority, influence, or  knowledge","answer" : "Purview"},
{"question": "Argue loudly about things that are not important","answer" : "Squabble"},
{"question": "Argue with someone in a friendly way","answer" : "Spar"},
{"question": "An arrangement of events or dates in the order of eir occurrence","answer" : "Chronology"},
{"question": "An arrangement of leaves, flowers, fruits, etc., in the shape of a circle that is  used for decoration","answer" : "Wreath"},
{"question": "An arrangement to meet somebody at a particular time and place","answer" : "Rendezvous"},
{"question": "Arrival of a large number of people","answer" : "Influx"},
{"question": "An art of growing ornamental, artificially dwarfed varieties of trees and shrubs  in pots","answer" : "Bonsai"},
{"question": "An art, science, or profession of teaching","answer" : "Pedagogy"},
{"question": "As compared with; as opposed to","answer" : "Vis-a-vis"},
{"question": "Asking for or demanding and taking (something) for one's use","answer" : "Requisition"},
{"question": "At or near the end of a piece of writing","answer" : "Ad fin"},
{"question": "Attacking on the reputation and integrity of someone or something","answer" : "Aspersion"},
{"question": "Attractive in a sexual way with large breasts and hips","answer" : "Voluptuous"},
{"question": "An attractively arranged bunch of flowers,especially one presented as a gift or  carried at a ceremony","answer" : "Bouquet"},
{"question": "Average or ordinary","answer" : "Run-of-the-mill        "},
{"question": "Back in which the spine is curved in an abnormal way","answer" : "Hunchback"},
{"question": "Bad or immoral behaviour or habits","answer" : "Vice"},
{"question": "Bad or immoral behaviour that involves sex, drugs, alcohol, etc.","answer" : "Debauchery"},
{"question": "Bad or unfavorable; not good","answer" : "Untoward"},
{"question": "Based on random choices or personal whims,rather than any reason or system","answer" : "  Arbitrary"},
{"question": "Based on what is known or seen when something is first considered or dealt  with","answer" : "Prima facie"},
{"question": "Basic equipment and structures (such as roads and bridges) that are needed for  a country,region, or organization to function properly","answer" : "Infrastructure"},
{"question": "Be a sign of (something that is beginning to happen or will happen soon)","answer" : " Herald"},
{"question": "Be angry or upset about something and to refuse to discuss it with other people ","answer" : "Sulk"},
{"question": "Be deprived of a close relation or friend through their death","answer" : "Bereave"},
{"question": "Be repeated several times as it is reflected off different surface","answer" : "Reverberate"},
{"question": "Beat or whip (someone) severely","answer" : "Flog"},
{"question": "Beautiful woman; the most beautiful woman in a particular place","answer" : "Belle"},
{"question": "Beginning or first appearance of something","answer" : "Dawning"},
{"question": "Beginning or origin of something","answer" : "Genesis"},
{"question": "Beginning to develop or exist","answer" : "Incipient"},
{"question": "Beginning to exist; recently formed or developed","answer" : "Nascent"},
{"question": "Behaviour that is accepted as socially or morally correct and proper","answer" : "Propriety"},
{"question": "Behaviour that shows low morals and a great love of pleasure, money, fame,  etc","answer" : "Decadence"},
{"question": "Behaviour in which somebody pretends to have moral standards or opinions  that they do not actually have","answer" : "Hypocrisy"},
{"question": "Behaviour, in particular sexual or legally dubious behaviour; considered  improper but not seriously so","answer" : "Hanky-panky"},
{"question": "Beliefs or ideas that are very important to a group","answer" : "Tenet"},
{"question": "Beliefs or opinions that do not agree with the official belief or opinion of a  particular religion","answer" : "Heresy"},
{"question": "Beliefs that particular events happen in a way that cannot be explained by  reason or science","answer" : "Superstition"},
{"question": "Belonging or relating to heaven","answer" : "Celestial"},
{"question": "Belonging to a foreign country, supposedly from another world; unfamiliar and  disturbing or distasteful","answer" : "Alien"},
{"question": "Belonging to a particular place rather than coming to it from somewhere else","answer" : " Indigenous     "},
{"question": "Belonging to the basic nature of someone or something","answer" : " Inherent"},
{"question": "Belonging to the middle class","answer" : "Bourgeois"},
{"question": "Below or beneath (something)","answer" : "Underneath"},
{"question": "Bending down or over; doing something that is not honest, fair, etc.","answer" : "Stoop"},
{"question": "Benefits which one enjoys or is entitled to on account of one's job or position","answer" : " Perquisite"},
{"question": "Best or most important part of something; the point of greatest success or  achievement","answer" : "Pinnacle"},
{"question": "Best or most important person or thing","answer" : "Numero uno"},
{"question": "Best or most important thing owned or produced by a particular organization","answer" : " Flagship"},
{"question": "Better than all others","answer" : "Par excellence"},
{"question": "Blaming or insulting (someone) in strong or violent language","answer" : "Vituperate"},
{"question": "Block of stone or wood that is used as the base for a pillar, statue, etc.","answer" : "Plinth"},
{"question": "Body of remedial substances used in the practice of medicine","answer" : "Materia  medica"},
{"question": "Books, articles, etc., that discuss a subject carefully and thoroughly","answer" : "Treatise"},
{"question": "Border or line that separates two things, such as types of work, groups of  people or areas of land","answer" : "Demarcation"},
{"question": "Boring or unpleasant work that does not require special skill and usually does  not pay much money","answer" : "Menial"},
{"question": "Bottom edge of a dress, skirt, or coat","answer" : "Hemline"},
{"question": "Break off (a meeting, legal case , or game) with the intention of resuming it  later","answer" : "Adjorn"},
{"question": "Brief and direct in a way that may seem rude or unfriendly","answer" : "Terse"},
{"question": "Brief and usually unplanned fight during a war","answer" : "Skirmish"},
{"question": "Brief time when an action or activity stops","answer" : "Lull"},
{"question": "Brief trips taken for pleasure","answer" : "Jaunt"},
{"question": "Brief trips that people take for fun usually as a group","answer" : "Outing"},
{"question": "Brief written messages or reports from one person or department in a company  or organization to another","answer" : "Memorandum"},
{"question": "Bringing (someone who is unconscious, not breathing, or close to death) back  to a conscious or active state again","answer" : "Resuscitate"},
{"question": "Broken parts of a vehicle, building, etc., that has been badly damaged or  destroyed","answer" : "Wreckage"},
{"question": "Brother or sister","answer" : "Sibling"},
{"question": "Building and the area of land that it is on, statement or idea that is accepted as  being true and that is used as the basis of an argument","answer" : "Premise"},
{"question": "Building in which grain is stored","answer" : "Granary"},
{"question": "Building in which the bodies of dead people are burned","answer" : "Crematorium     "},
{"question": "Building or chamber above or below the ground in which a dead body is kept","answer" : " Tomb"},
{"question": "Building or room in which images of stars, planets, etc., are shown on a high,  curved ceiling","answer" : "Planetarium"},
{"question": "Building that is used for Jewish religious services","answer" : "Synagogue"},
{"question": "Building where aircrafts are kept","answer" : "Hangar"},
{"question": "Business of making fashionable and expensive clothes for women","answer" : "Haute  couture"},
{"question": "Businesses that make money through illegal activities, loud, unpleasant noise","answer" : " Racket"},
{"question": "By or for each person","answer" : "Per capita      "},
{"question": "Caption to a photograph or other illustration","answer" : "Cutline"},
{"question": "Card from the pack that has been chosen as the most valuable for a particular  card game","answer" : "Trump"},
{"question": "Care or maintenance of buildings, equipment,etc","answer" : "Unkeep"},
{"question": "Careful and persistent works or efforts","answer" : "Diligence"},
{"question": "Careful plans or methods for achieving a particular goal usually over a long  period of time","answer" : "Strategy"},
{"question": "Cause (a material) to be filled or soaked with something","answer" : "Impregnate"},
{"question": "Cause (someone or something) to receive or take in a large amount of things at  the same time","answer" : "Inundate"},
{"question": "Cause (someone) to fall down or be turned over","answer" : "Upend"},
{"question": "Cause (things or people) to separate and go in different directions","answer" : "Scatter"},
{"question": "Cause of pain or harm","answer" : "Affliction"},
{"question": "Centre of public attention","answer" : "Limelight"},
{"question": "Ceremony held for a dead person","answer" : "Funeral"},
{"question": "Ceremony held in a university or college when students receive their degrees","answer" : " Convocation"},
{"question": "Ceremony in which a crown is placed on the head of a new king or queen","answer" : " Coronation"},
{"question": "Certain to die","answer" : "Mortal"},
{"question": "Certain to work properly or succeed","answer" : "Infallible"},
{"question": "Changing (something good) so that it is no longer as what it was or should be","answer" : " Pervert"},
{"question": "Charging an important public figure with a serious crime","answer" : "Impeach     "},
{"question": "Changing (something) slightly in order to improve it; to make small  adjustments to (something)","answer" : "Tweak"},
{"question": "Changing an earlier statement, opinion or promise because of pressure from  somebody/something","answer" : "Backtrack"},
{"question": "Changing direction quickly or suddenly","answer" : "Veer"},
{"question": "Changing from one state or condition to another","answer" : "Transition"},
{"question": "Changing moods quickly and often","answer" : "Mercurical"},
{"question": "Character and atmosphere of a place","answer" : "Ambience"},
{"question": "Cheerful friendliness; geniality","answer" : "Bonhomie"},
{"question": "Chemical processes that occur within a living organism in order to maintain  life","answer" : " Metabolism"},
{"question": "Claim or a piece of evidence that one was elsewhere when an act, typically a  criminal one , is alleged to have taken place; excuse or pretext","answer" : "Alibi"},
{"question": "Clear message or request for people to do something","answer" : "Clarion call"},
{"question": "Clever trick or plan that is used to get someone to do something or to gain an  advantage over someone","answer" : "ploy"},
{"question": "Climb or moving with difficulty or a lot of effort, using one's hands and feet","answer" : " Clamber"},
{"question": "Close friend one has worked with, been in the military with, etc.","answer" : "Comrade"},
{"question": "Close relationship with someone or something","answer" : "Communion"},
{"question": "Close - knit group of interrelated families, large family, or a group of people  who are connected because of a particular thing","answer" : "clan"},
{"question": "Clothes, especially fine or formal ones","answer" : "attire"},
{"question": "Collecting or forming into a mass or group","answer" : " Agglomerate"},
{"question": "Collectable object such as a piece of furniture or work of art that has a high  value because of its age and quality","answer" : " Antique"},
{"question": "Collection of different things","answer" : "Potpourri"},
{"question": "Collection of historical documents or records providing information about a  place, institution, orgroup of people","answer" : "Archive"},
{"question": "Collection of things (such as photographs, stories, facts, etc.) that have been  gathered together and presented as a group especially in the form of a book","answer" : " Compendium"},
{"question": "Collection of things, which may be similar or different","answer" : "Collage"},
{"question": "Collection of weapons and military equipment","answer" : "Arsenals"},
{"question": "Collection of written or spoken texts","answer" : "Corpus"},
{"question": "Combination of events, state of affairs","answer" : "Conjuncture"},
{"question": "Come at a later time; to happen as a result","answer" : "Ensure"},
{"question": "Comparing between one thing and another, typically for the purpose of  explanation or clarification","answer" : "Analogy"},
{"question": "Compelling attractiveness or charm that can inspire devotion in others","answer" : " Charisma     "},
{"question": "Competition for young women in which their beauty, personal qualities and  skills are judged","answer" : "Pageant"},
{"question": "Complete change of attitude or opinion","answer" : "Volte-Face"},
{"question": "Complete control of the entire supply of goods or of a service in a certain area  or market","answer" : "Monopoly"},
{"question": "Complete freedom to act as one wishes","answer" : "Carte blanche"},
{"question": "Complete lists of items, typically one in alphabetical or other systematic order","answer" : " Catalogue"},
{"question": "Complete range of different opinions,people, etc.","answer" : "Spectrum"},
{"question": "Completely unwilling to change","answer" : "Intransigent"},
{"question": "Complex disputes or arguments","answer" : "Imbroglio"},
{"question": "Complicated and confusing system of connected passage","answer" : "Maze"},
{"question": "Complicated or unpleasant situations that is difficult to get out of or to move  through","answer" : "Morass"},
{"question": "Comprising or relating to all sorts or varieties","answer" : "Omnifarious"},
{"question": "Conceal the nature or existence of (a feeling or situation)","answer" : "Disguise"},
{"question": "Concentrated artillery bombardment over a wide area : large number of  something, such as questions or comments, that are directed at somebody very  quickly, one after the other, often in an aggressive way","answer" : "Barrage"},
{"question": "Conclusion or opinions that are formed because of known facts or evidence","answer" : " Inference"},
{"question": "Condition in which a part of one's body becomes red, swollen, and painful","answer" : "  Inflammation"},
{"question": "Condition in which someone is not able to think normally because of being  drunk, drugged, tired, etc.","answer" : "Stupor"},
{"question": "Confused struggles or fights involving many people","answer" : "Melee"},
{"question": "Confusing or difficult problem","answer" : "Conundrum"},
{"question": "Confusing or meaningless words or activities","answer" : "Mumbo-jumbo"},
{"question": "Connected with particular circumstances","answer" : " Circumstantial"},
{"question": "Connected with young people who are not yet adults","answer" : "Juvenile"},
{"question": "Consequences or after-effects of a significant and unpleasant event","answer" : " Aftermath"},
{"question": "Consisting of or using both letters and numerals","answer" : "Alphanumeric"},
{"question": "Consisting of things or people that are all the same or all of the same type","answer" : " Homogeneous"},
{"question": "Contests, disputes, competitions, etc., in which neither side can gain an  advantage or win","answer" : "Stalemate"},
{"question": "Continual increase in the price of goods and services","answer" : "Inflation"},
{"question": "Continuing without stopping","answer" : "Incessant"},
{"question": "Continuous rattling sound as of hard objects falling or striking each other","answer" : " Clatter     "},
{"question": "Control or affect (something, such as a game or election) in a dishonest way in  order to get a desired result","answer" : "Rig"},
{"question": "Controlling or influencing a situation in a skilful but sometimes dishonest way","answer" : " Manoeuvre"},
{"question": "Controlled breeding and rearing of fish.","answer" : "Pisciculture"},
{"question": "Conversations in which clever statements and replies are made quickly","answer" : " Repartee"},
{"question": "Correcting something that is unfair or wrong","answer" : "Redress"},
{"question": "Corrupt behaviour in a position of trust, especially in public office","answer" : " Malversation"},
{"question": "Courage or bravery","answer" : "Valour"},
{"question": "Courtesy and considerate behaviour towards others","answer" : "Comity"},
{"question": "Course of action leading nowhere","answer" : "Blind alley"},
{"question": "Covered passages with arches along one or both sides","answer" : "arcade"},
{"question": "Covered with decoration","answer" : "Ornate"},
{"question": "Created or done for a particular purpose as necessary","answer" : "Ad hoc"},
{"question": "Crime of getting money from someone by the use of force or threat","answer" : "Extortion"},
{"question": "Crime of trying to overthrow one's country's government or of helping one's  country's enemies during war","answer" : " Treason"},
{"question": "Crimes or other morally wrong acts : illegal or immoral behavior especially by  young people","answer" : "Delinquency"},
{"question": "Cruel and unfair treatment by people with power over others","answer" : "Tyranny"},
{"question": "Cry very loudly and noisily","answer" : "Squall"},
{"question": "Curved paths along which something (such as a rocket) moves through the air  or through space","answer" : "Trajectory"},
{"question": "Curved paths followed by a planet or an object as it moves around another  planet, star, moon, etc","answer" : " Orbit"},
{"question": "Customs or a way of acting or doing things that is widely accepted and  followed","answer" : "Convention"},
{"question": "Customers of a shop, bar, or place of entertainment","answer" : "Clientele"},
{"question": "Cut made in something","answer" : "Incision    "},
{"question": "Dance or musical performance","answer" : "Recital"},
{"question": "Dangers or problems that are hidden or not obvious at first","answer" : "Pitfall"},
{"question": "Dark and dirty : not fresh or clean","answer" : "Dingy"},
{"question": "Dark and underground prisons in castles","answer" : "Dungeon     "},
{"question": "Date or time when something must be finished : the last day, hour, or minute on  that something will be accepted","answer" : "Deadline"},
{"question": "Days when day and night are of the same length","answer" : "Equinox"},
{"question": "Dead bodies of animals","answer" : "Carcass"},
{"question": "Dead persons who leave the grave at night to bite and suck the blood of living  people","answer" : "Vampire"},
{"question": "Decayed mixture of plants (such as leaves and grass) that is used to improve the  soil in a garden","answer" : "Compost"},
{"question": "Decayed with usually a very bad or disgusting smell","answer" : "Putrid"},
{"question": "Deceiving or to trick (someone) to persuade (someone) by telling lies","answer" : "Con(v)"},
{"question": "Deep unconscious state, usually lasting a long time and caused by serious  illness or injury","answer" : "Coma"},
{"question": "Deep, wet sand into which heavy objects sink easily","answer" : "Quicksand"},
{"question": "Deeply religious : devoted to a particular religion","answer" : "Devout"},
{"question": "Defeating (someone or something) easily and Throughly","answer" : "Trounce"},
{"question": "Defeating and gaining control of (someone or something) by the use of force","answer" : " Subjugate"},
{"question": "Defeating or tricking (someone) by being more intelligent or clever","answer" : "Outsmart"},
{"question": "Delay doing something until a later time because one does not want to do it,  because one is lazy","answer" : "Procrastinate"},
{"question": "Describing (someone or something) as unimportant, weak, bad, etc","answer" : "Disparage"},
{"question": "Designed or intended to teach people something","answer" : "Didactic"},
{"question": "Desire to cause harm to another person","answer" : "Malice"},
{"question": "Determined not to change one's opinion or attitude; difficult to deal with,  remove, etc.","answer" : "Stubborn"},
{"question": "Developing friendlier relations between countries or groups of people who have  been enemies","answer" : "Rapprochement"},
{"question": "Dictionary of the special terms in a particular field or job","answer" : "Glossary"},
{"question": "Die because one is unable to breathe","answer" : "Suffocate"},
{"question": "Difference between two opposite things : a division into two opposite groups","answer" : " Dichotomy"},
{"question": "Difference especially between things that should be the same","answer" : "Discrepancy"},
{"question": "Difficult and unpleasant to do or deal with","answer" : "Onerous"},
{"question": "Difficult to handle, control, or deal with because of being large, heavy, or  complex","answer" : "Unwieldy"},
{"question": "Difficult to understand : having or seeming to have a hidden meaning","answer" : "Cryptic"},
{"question": "Dilemma or difficult circumstances from which there is no escape because of  mutually conflicting or dependent conditions","answer" : "Catch-22"},
{"question": "Direct descent from an ancestor; ancestry or pedigree","answer" : "Lineage"},
{"question": "Disappointing end to an exciting or impressive series of events","answer" : " Anticlimax  "},
{"question": "Disease or disorder that involves a particular group of signs and symptoms","answer" : " Syndrome"},
{"question": "Disease that spreads over a whole country or the whole world","answer" : "Pandemic"},
{"question": "Disguising of military personnel, equipment, and installations by painting or  covering them to make them blend in with their surrounding","answer" : "Camouflage"},
{"question": "Dishonest or immoralpersons","answer" : "Sleaze"},
{"question": "Displaying wealth, knowledge, etc., in a way that is meant to attract attention,  admiration, or envy","answer" : "Ostentatious"},
{"question": "Distance of a place east or west of the Greenwich meridian, measured in  degrees","answer" : "Longitude"},
{"question": "Distance of a place north or south of the equator (= the line around the world  dividing north and south), measured in degrees","answer" : "Latitude"},
{"question": "Doing activities for fun or enjoyment","answer" : "Play-off"},
{"question": "Doing better than (someone or something) : to be more successful than  (someone or something)","answer" : "Outdo"},
{"question": "Doing something that is not allowed : to disobey a command or law","answer" : " Transgress"},
{"question": "Doctor's opinion about how someone will recover from an illness or injury","answer" : " Prognosis"},
{"question": "Done or given because one wants to and not because one is forced to","answer" : " Voluntary"},
{"question": "Dramatic works in which all or most of the words are sung to music; works of  this type as an art form or entertainment","answer" : "Opera"},
{"question": "Drawing or pictures that show only the shape of an object","answer" : "Outline"},
{"question": "Dull and ordinary","answer" : "Mundane"},
{"question": "Dull or socially ineptperson, especially someone who is excessively studious","answer" : " Spod          "},
{"question": "Eager to own and collect things","answer" : "Acquisitive"},
{"question": "Easily affected, influenced, or harmed by something","answer" : "Susceptible"},
{"question": "Easily annoyed or angered and likely to argue","answer" : "Truculent"},
{"question": "Easily hurt or harmed physically, mentally, or emotionally : open to attack,  harm, or damage","answer" : "Vulnerable"},
{"question": "Easily managed or controlled : willing to learn or be guided by another","answer" : " Tractable   "},
{"question": "Eating both plants and animals : eager to learn about many different things","answer" : " Omnivorous"},
{"question": "Economic situations where there is high inflation (= prices rising continuously)  but no increase in the jobs that are available or in business activity","answer" : " Stagflation"},
{"question": "Effective from a particular date in the past","answer" : "Retrospective"},
{"question": "Elaborate or glib speeches or stories, typically those used by a salesperson","answer" : " Spiel"},
{"question": "E-mails that are not wanted : an e-mail that is sent to large numbers of people  and that consists mostly of advertising","answer" : "Spam"},
{"question": "Embarrassing social mistake","answer" : "Faux pas"},
{"question": "Ending a romantic relationship with (someone) in a sudden and painful way","answer" : " Jilt"},
{"question": "Ending an organization or group (such as a club)","answer" : "Disband"},
{"question": "End or failure of an institution, an idea, a company, etc. : death of a person","answer" : " Demise"},
{"question": "Enjoy (something) for a long time","answer" : "Savour"},
{"question": "Enjoying oneself or celebrating in a noisy or boisterous way","answer" : "Roister"},
{"question": "Enjoyable in a lively or noisy way","answer" : "Rollicking"},
{"question": "Enjoyments that someone gets from being violent or cruel or from causing pain ","answer" : "Sadism"},
{"question": "Entering (someone) as a member of or being a participant in something","answer" : " Enroll"},
{"question": "Entering or appearing somewhere suddenly and with a lot of force","answer" : "Irrupt"},
{"question": "Enthusiastic and vocal supporters of someone or something","answer" : "Cheerleader"},
{"question": "Enthusiastic clapping by an audience as a sign of their approval","answer" : "Ovation"},
{"question": "Error in the way a law, rule, or contract is written that makes it possible for  some people to legally avoid obeying it","answer" : "LOOPHOLE"},
{"question": "Events causing great and usually sudden damage or suffering; a disaster","answer" : " catastrophe"},
{"question": "Events involving destruction or damage on a catastrophic scale","answer" : "apocalypse"},
{"question": "Events marked by festivities or celebration","answer" : "fiesta"},
{"question": "Event or a short period of time that is important or unusual","answer" : "episode"},
{"question": "Events or situations in which many people are killed and many things are  destroyc espicially by fire","answer" : " holocaust"},
{"question": "Events that may or may not happen","answer" : "contingency"},
{"question": "Exact or very close copy of something","answer" : "Replica"},
{"question": "Examinations intended to qualify successful candidates for higher education","answer" : "Baccalaureate"},
{"question": "Examples that represent or express something very well","answer" : "Epitome"},
{"question": "Excessive emotional or psychological reliance on a partner","answer" : "Codependency     "},
{"question": "Exchanging goods, property, services, etc. for other goods, etc. without using  money","answer" : "Barter"},
{"question": "Excluding (someone) from a group","answer" : "Ostracize"},
{"question": "Existing as a basic part of a person's nature or character","answer" : "Inbred"},
{"question": "Existing from the beginning of time : very ancient","answer" : "Primordial"},
{"question": "Existing or continuing in the same way for a long time","answer" : "Perennial"},
{"question": "Existing or happening in the same time period","answer" : "Contemporary"},
{"question": "Existing, but not yet very noticeable, active or well developed","answer" : "Latent"},
{"question": "Experiences that are very unpleasant or difficult","answer" : "Ordeal"},
{"question": "Experienced or felt by watching, hearing about, or reading about someone else  rather than by doing something yourself","answer" : "Vicarious"},
{"question": "Expressing doubts about whether something is right, honest, etc.","answer" : "Impugn"},
{"question": "Expressing severe disapprovals of (someone or something), especially in a  formal statement","answer" : "Censure"},
{"question": "Expressing feelings or opinions in a very loud or forceful way","answer" : "Vociferous"},
{"question": "Expressing opinions or criticism in a very forceful and often annoying or  unpleasant way","answer" : "Strident"},
{"question": "Expressions designed to call something to mind without mentioning it  explicitly : an indirect or passing reference","answer" : "Allusion"},
{"question": "Expressions of strong anger or disapproval by many people","answer" : "Outcry"},
{"question": "Extensive groups of islands","answer" : "Archipelago"},
{"question": "Extra vote given by a chairperson to decide an issue when the votes on each  side are equal","answer" : "Casting vote"},
{"question": "Extracting money from (someone) by fine or taxation","answer" : "Mulct"},
{"question": "Extreme anger : a strong feeling of unhappiness because of something bad,  hurtful, or morally wrong","answer" : "Outrage"},
{"question": "Extreme physical or mental sufferings","answer" : "Agony"},
{"question": "Extreme self confidence or audacity (usually used approvingly)","answer" : "Chutzpah"},
{"question": "Extremely easy tasks","answer" : "Cinch"},
{"question": "Extremely excited and enthusiastic about doing something","answer" : "Gung ho"},
{"question": "Extremely good and deserving to be admired and copied","answer" : "Exemplary"},
{"question": "Extremely or unusually small","answer" : "Diminutive"},
{"question": "Extremely strong dislikes or fears of someone or something","answer" : "Phobia          "},
{"question": "Facts or the process of ending or being brought to an end","answer" : "Cessation"},
{"question": "Failing to show proper respect and courtesy","answer" : "Impudent     "},
{"question": "Failure to fulfil an obligation : something that happens or is done when nothing  else has been done or can be done","answer" : "Default"},
{"question": "Familiar or humorous names given to a person or thing instead of the real name ","answer" : "Nickname"},
{"question": "Families of rulers who rule over a country for a long period of time","answer" : "Dynasty"},
{"question": "Famous persons, especially in entertainment or sport","answer" : "Celebrity"},
{"question": "Farmers in the past who owned a small amount of land : very good, hard, and  valuable work that someone does especially to support a cause, to help a team,  etc.","answer" : "Yeoman"},
{"question": "Features (such as mountains and rivers) in an area of land","answer" : "Topography"},
{"question": "Feeling a strong desire or wish for something or to do something","answer" : "Yearn"},
{"question": "Feeling nervous because the ending is not known until the final moment","answer" : "Nail- biting"},
{"question": "Feeling or showing great sadness because someone has died","answer" : "Mourn"},
{"question": "Feeling sorrow or regreting for (something)","answer" : "Rue"},
{"question": "Feeling of being sorry for doing something bad or wrong in the past","answer" : "Remorse"},
{"question": "Feelings of deep anxiety or dread, typically an unfocused one about the human  condition or the state of the world in general","answer" : "Angst"},
{"question": "Feelings of doubt or uncertainty about whether Qualm one is doing the right  thing   ","answer":"Qualm"},
{"question": "Feelings of enjoyment and enthusiasm","answer" : "Zest"},
{"question": "Feelings of foolish or very strong love or admiration for someone or something ","answer" : "Infatuation"},
{"question": "Feelings of great happiness and excitement","answer" : "Euphoria"},
{"question": "Feelings of guilt or regret","answer" : "Compunction"},
{"question": "Feelings of like or dislike for someone or something especially when it is not  reasonable or logical","answer" : "Prejudice"},
{"question": "Feelings of sadness mixed with pleasure and affection when one thinks of  happy times in the past","answer" : "Nostalgia"},
{"question": "Feelings of strong dislike or disapproval of someone or something you think  does not deserve respect","answer" : "Disdain"},
{"question": "Feelings or beliefs that bad things will happen in the future","answer" : "Pessimism"},
{"question": "Feelings or belief that good things will happen in the future","answer" : "Optimism"},
{"question": "Feelings or expressing overwhelming happiness or joyful excitement","answer" : "Ecstatic"},
{"question": "Feelings or a particular quality that is very noticeable and seems to surround a  person or place","answer" : "Aura"},
{"question": "Feelings or showing a lack of courage or confidence","answer" : "Timid"},
{"question": "Feelings that someone or something gives you","answer" : "Vibe"},
{"question": "Female ballet dancers","answer" : "Danseuse"},
{"question": "Fictitious or factual works describing a series of events","answer" : "Chronicle"},
{"question": "Fights between women","answer" : "Catfight     "},
{"question": "Fights, briefly and usually not very seriously","answer" : "Scuffle"},
{"question": "Figures shaped like a human body that is used for making or displaying clothes ","answer" : "Mannequin"},
{"question": "Filled with or showing sexual desire","answer" : "Lascivious"},
{"question": "First time an actor, musician, athlete, etc., does something in public or for the  public","answer" : "Debut"},
{"question": "Fixed sum of money paid to someone each year, typically for the rest of their  life","answer" : "Annuity"},
{"question": "Flat cases for carrying documents or drawings, investments that are owned by a  person or organization","answer" : "Portfolio"},
{"question": "Fleet of warships","answer" : "Armada"},
{"question": "Flowing out of something in a fast and forceful way","answer" : "Spew"},
{"question": "Following, watching, and bothering (someone) constantly in a way that is  frightening, dangerous, etc.","answer" : "Stalk"},
{"question": "Food that a person or animal usually eats","answer" : " Diet"},
{"question": "Food that is cooked in a particular way, style of cooking","answer" : "Cuisine"},
{"question": "Foolish talks or ideas.","answer" : " Guff"},
{"question": "Foolish, confused, or meaningless words","answer" : "Gibberish"},
{"question": "For an intervening or temporary period of time","answer" : "Ad interim"},
{"question": "Forcing someone to go somewhere with you, often using threats or violence","answer" : " Abduction"},
{"question": "Forceful or angry speeches","answer" : "Harangue"},
{"question": "Forming An opinion about something without definitely knowing the truth","answer" : " Surmise"},
{"question": "Form of punishments or tortures that involved caning the soles of someone's  feet","answer" : "Bastinado"},
{"question": "Formal acts or the process of placing someone into a new job, position,  government office,","answer" : "Induction"},
{"question": "Formal ceremonies or series of acts that are always performed in the same way ","answer" : "Ritual"},
{"question": "Formal meetings in which representatives or experts discuss important matters,  make decisions, etc.","answer" : "Congress"},
{"question": "Formal processions ofpeople walking, on horseback, or riding in vehicles","answer" : " Cavalcade"},
{"question": "Formally choosing (someone) as a candidate for a job, position, office, etc.","answer" : " Nominate"},
{"question": "Formations of clear and distinct sounds in speech","answer" : "Articulation"},
{"question": "Fortresses, typically one on high ground above a city","answer" : "Citadel"},
{"question": "Formal and serious promises to tell the truth or to do something","answer" : "Oath"},
{"question": "Fraudulent or dishonest acts or practices","answer" : "Rort   "},
{"question": "Fraudulent practices of sending emails purporting to be from reputable  companies in order to induce individuals to reveal personal information","answer" : " Phishing"},
{"question": "Freedom from being required to do something that others are required to do","answer" : " Exemption"},
{"question": "Freedom from punishment, harm, or loss","answer" : "Impunity"},
{"question": "Freedom to do something the way you want to do it","answer" : "Leeway"},
{"question": "Friendly relationships","answer" : "Rapport"},
{"question": "Friendly remarks and jokes","answer" : "Banter"},
{"question": "Full and wide view of something","answer" : "panorama"},
{"question": "Full of anger, arguments and bad feelings","answer" : "Acrimonious"},
{"question": "Full of clever tricks : very clever","answer" : "Wily"},
{"question": "Full of hate or anger, extremely or excessively harsh or strong","answer" : "Virulent"},
{"question": "Funny and clever","answer" : "Witty"},
{"question": "Funny plays or movies about ridiculous situations","answer" : " Farce       "},
{"question": "General laws, rules, principles, or criteria by which something is judged","answer" : " Canon"},
{"question": "General or basic quality or meaning of something","answer" : "Tenor"},
{"question": "Generous and friendly treatment of visitors and guests","answer" : "Hospitality"},
{"question": "Genuine, real or legal; not false","answer" : "Bona fide"},
{"question": "Girlfriends of criminals","answer" : "Moll"},
{"question": "Giving a brief summary of something","answer" : "Recapitulate"},
{"question": "Giving or being a sign of (something that will happen or develop in the future) ","answer" : "Presage"},
{"question": "Giving somebody a signal using your finger or hand, especially to tell them to  move nearer or to follow you","answer" : "Beckon"},
{"question": "Giving up (something) : to give (something, such as power, control, or  possession) to another person or group","answer" : "Relinquish"},
{"question": "Giving help or support to the main group of workers","answer" : "Auxiliary"},
{"question": "Going in a direction that is away from a group or from the place where one  should be","answer" : "Stray"},
{"question": "Going on someone's land without permission","answer" : "Trespass"},
{"question": "Goods that are bought and sold","answer" : "Merchandise"},
{"question": "Government departments that control public money","answer" : "Exchequer"},
{"question": "Governments formed by two or more political parties working together","answer" : " Coalition   "},
{"question": "Government officials who are the representative of his or her country in a  foreign country","answer" : "Consul"},
{"question": "Government orders that limit trade in some way","answer" : "Embargo"},
{"question": "Gradual increase in noise : the loudest point of a period of continuous noise","answer" : " Crescendo"},
{"question": "Gradual reduction in the size of a business, activity, etc.","answer" : "Runown"},
{"question": "Great and often wild or uncontrolled activities","answer" : "Frenzy"},
{"question": "Great disaster or complete failure","answer" : "Debacle"},
{"question": "Great number of things or people","answer" : "Multitude"},
{"question": "Great technical skill and brilliance shown in a performance or activity","answer" : " Bravura"},
{"question": "Great work : the greatest achievement of an artist , or a writer","answer" : "Magnum opus"},
{"question": "Groups of animals or plants that are similar and can produce young animals or  plants","answer" : "Species"},
{"question": "groups of members of the public who listen to the facts of a case in a court and  decide whether or not somebody is guilty of a crime","answer" : "Jury"},
{"question": "Groups of military ships commanded by the same person","answer" : "Fleet"},
{"question": "Groups of musicians who play usually classical mt sic together and who are led  by a conductor","answer" : "orchestra"},
{"question": "Groups of officials led by an ambassador who represent their government in a  foreign country :building in which an embassy works","answer" : "embassy"},
{"question": "Groups of people or businesses that work together","answer" : "Syndicate"},
{"question": "Groups of people who are doing something together","answer" : "Platoon"},
{"question": "Groups of people who are the leaders of an action or movement in society,  politics, art,","answer" : "Vanguard"},
{"question": "Groups of people who are together for a particular","answer" : "Posse"},
{"question": "Groups of people who go with and assist an important person","answer" : "Entourage"},
{"question": "Groups of people who have gathered to watch or listen to something (a play,  concert, somebody speaking, etc.)","answer" : "Audience"},
{"question": "Groups of people who have the same job, interests, etc.","answer" : "Fraternity"},
{"question": "Groups of people who operate a ship, airplane, or train","answer" : "Crew"},
{"question": "Groups cf people who share a common feature or aspect of behaviour","answer" : "Cohort"},
{"question": "Groups of people with shared concerns within a political party or larger  organization","answer" : "Caucus"},
{"question": "Groups of people, companies, etc., that agree to work together","answer" : "Consortium"},
{"question": "Groups of people, countries, organizations, etc., that are joined together in  some activity or effort","answer" : "Confederation"},
{"question": "Groups of people, especially traders or pilgrims,travelling together across a  desert in Asia or North Africa","answer" : "Caravan"},
{"question": "Groups of separate companies that agree to increase profits by fixing prices and  not competing with each other","answer" : "Cartel     "},
{"question": "Groups of singers or dancers performing together in a supporting role in a  musical or opera","answer" : "Chorus"},
{"question": "Groups of vehicles or ships that are travelling together usually for protection","answer" : " Convoy"},
{"question": "Groups or organization of nations or people united for a purpose","answer" : "League"},
{"question": "Groups within a larger group that have different ideas and opinions than the  rest of the group","answer" : "Faction"},
{"question": "Guiding beliefs of a person, group, or organization","answer" : "Ethos    "},
{"question": "Happening after death, medical examination of the body of a dead person to  determine the cause of death","answer" : "Postmortem"},
{"question": "Happening as a result of something","answer" : "Consequent"},
{"question": "Happening at the same time","answer" : "Concurrent"},
{"question": "Happening often but not regularly : not constant or steady","answer" : "Sporadic"},
{"question": "Happening or appearing again and again","answer" : "Recurrent"},
{"question": "Happening or appearing in many places and not unusual : very common or  ordinary","answer" : "Common place"},
{"question": "Happening or popular at a particular time","answer" : "Du jour"},
{"question": "Happening, done, or published after someone's death","answer" : "Posthumous"},
{"question": "Happy and enjoyable scenes or experience","answer" : "Idyll"},
{"question": "Happy and lively in a way that is attractive","answer" : "Vivacious"},
{"question": "Harming (someone) through sexual contact to touch (someone) in a sexual and  improper way","answer" : "Molest"},
{"question": "Harsh and angry words","answer" : "Vitriolic"},
{"question": "Harsh criticisms that show a lack of respect or approval for someone or  something","answer" : "Scorn"},
{"question": "Harsh discordant mixture of sounds","answer" : "Cacophony"},
{"question": "Harsh or critical statements about someone","answer" : "Obloquy"},
{"question": "Having (something) as a part, step, or result","answer" : "Entail"},
{"question": "Having a speech problem that causes one to repeat the beginning sound of  some words","answer" : "Stutter"},
{"question": "Having A dull 01 uninteteiting appearance not attractivc, or stylish","answer" : "Dowdy"},
{"question": "Having a god or helpful result especially after something unpleasant has  happened","answer" : "Salutary"},
{"question": "Having a pleasant, spicy taste interesting and exciting","answer" : "Piquant"},
{"question": "Having a strong and unpleasant smell or taste front no longer being fresh","answer" : " Rancid     "},
{"question": "Having a strong, sharp taste or smell","answer" : "Pungent"},
{"question": "Having a very appealing taste or smell","answer" : "Luscious"},
{"question": "Having a very noticeable quality that attrats a lot of attention","answer" : "Flamboyant"},
{"question": "Having an obstinately uncooperative attitude towards authority or discipline","answer" : " Recalcitrant"},
{"question": "Having complete or unlimited power","answer" : "Omnipotent"},
{"question": "Having fair hair and a light complexion","answer" : "Blonde"},
{"question": "Having many twists and turns : compliLated. long, and confusing","answer" : "Tortuous"},
{"question": "Having mixed feelings or contradictory ideas about something or someone","answer" : " Ambivalent"},
{"question": "Having no legal power","answer" : "Nutt"},
{"question": "Having no useful purpose","answer" : "Otiose"},
{"question": "Having or relating to two sides affecting both sides, involving two parties,  especially countries","answer" : "Bilateral"},
{"question": "Having or showing a desire to hurt someone who has hurt or caused problems  for you","answer" : "Vindictive"},
{"question": "Having or showing a lot of courage or determination","answer" : "Plucky"},
{"question": "Having or showing a lot of violence and blood","answer" : "Gory"},
{"question": "Having or showing an ability to understand difficult ideas and situations and to  make good decisions","answer" : "Sagacious"},
{"question": "Having or showing courage : very brave or courageous","answer" : "valiant"},
{"question": "Having or showing knowledge that is learned by studying","answer" : "erudite"},
{"question": "Having people of different types or from different countries, and influenced by  their culture : showing an interest in different cultures, ideas","answer" : "cosmopolitian"},
{"question": "Having the letters q, w, e, r, t, and y arranged in a ,Oweitt row in the top row of  letter keys","answer" : "querty"},
{"question": "Having the qualities or appearance considered to be typical of men","answer" : "Masculine"},
{"question": "Having very fixed beliefs and being unlikely or unwilling to change them","answer" : " Hardliner"},
{"question": "Heavy automatic guns that fire shells from an aircraft or tank","answer" : "Cannon"},
{"question": "Height of an object or point in relation to sea level or ground level","answer" : "Altitude"},
{"question": "Helping someone or something pay for the costs of (something)","answer" : "Subsidize"},
{"question": "Highest point in the development of something :a climax or culmination","answer" : " Apogee"},
{"question": "Highest point of a mountain : the top of a mountain","answer" : "Summit"},
{"question": "History of the family members in a person's or animal's past especially when it  is good or impressive","answer" : "Pedigree"},
{"question": "Hitting (someone or something) very hard with a stick, whip, etc","answer" : "Thrash"},
{"question": "Hitting (someone) on the buttocks with one's hand as a form of punishment","answer" : " Spank     "},
{"question": "Hitting or beating something or someone and make a loud, deep sound","answer" : " Thump"},
{"question": "Hitting something with a loud, dull sound","answer" : "Thud"},
{"question": "Honor or fame given for some achievement","answer" : "Laurel"},
{"question": "Honor or respect that is felt for or shown to (someone or something)","answer" : " Reverence"},
{"question": "Hopeful or romantic in a way that is not practical","answer" : "Quixotic"},
{"question": "Houses or part of a house in which the women of a Muslim household live","answer" : " Harem"},
{"question": "Houses where men visit prostitutes","answer" : "Brothel"},
{"question": "Humour that shows the weaknesses or bad qualities of a person, gOvernment,  society, etc.","answer" : "Satire"},
{"question": "Humorous in a clever and often ironic way","answer" : "Wry"},
{"question": "Humorous rhyming poem of five lines","answer" : "Limerick"},
{"question": "Hundredth anniversary of a significant event","answer" : "Centenary"},
{"question": "Husband's (or wife's) provision for a spouse after separation or divorce :  maintenance","answer" : "Alimony       "},
{"question": "Ideas about doing something that is far removed from normal reality","answer" : "Fantasy"},
{"question": "Ideas or beliefs that people are born again with a different body after death","answer" : " Reincarnation"},
{"question": "Ideas or inventions which are considered to be a particular person's creation","answer" : " Brainchild"},
{"question": "Ideas or sets of beliefs that guide the actions of a person or group","answer" : "Credo"},
{"question": "Idea or a set of principles or religious beliefs","answer" : "Creed"},
{"question": "Ideas or theories that are not proven but that leads to further study or discussion ","answer" : "Hypothesis"},
{"question": "Ideas suggested by a word in addition to its main meaning","answer" : "Connotation"},
{"question": "Ideas or statements that are often false or exaggerated and that are spread in  order to help a cause, a political leader, a government, etc.","answer" : "Propaganda"},
{"question": "Ideas or stories that are not true but that many people have heard or read","answer" : " Folklore"},
{"question": "(Illness) persisting for a long time or constantly recurring","answer" : "Chronic"},
{"question": "Imaginary places in which the government, laws, and social conditions are  perfect","answer" : "Utopia"},
{"question": "Imaginary sea creatures that have a woman's head and body and a fish's tail  instead of legs","answer" : "Mermaid   "},
{"question": "Impartial advisers to a court of law in a particular case","answer" : "Amicus curiae"},
{"question": "Important, real, or meaningful","answer" : "Substantive"},
{"question": "Impossible to defeat or discourage","answer" : "Indomitable"},
{"question": "Impossible to defeat or overcome","answer" : "INVINCIBLE"},
{"question": "Impossible to harm, damage, or defeat","answer" : "INVULNERABLE"},
{"question": "Impossible 'to solve or get control of : impossible to overcome","answer" : " INSURMOUNTABLE"},
{"question": "Impressive display or range of a particular type of thing","answer" : "ARRAY"},
{"question": "In a careless and unplanned way","answer" : "WILLY NILLY"},
{"question": "In a confused and careless way","answer" : "HELTER-SKELTER"},
{"question": "In a state of tremulous excitement","answer" : "AFLUTTER"},
{"question": "In a very bad condition and needing to be repaired","answer" : "RAMSHACKLE"},
{"question": "In an uncertain or undecided state or condition","answer" : "LIMBO"},
{"question": "In great disorder or confusion","answer" : "TOPSY-TURVY"},
{"question": "In preparation or progress happening or beginning to happen","answer" : "AFOOT"},
{"question": "In a very bad condition because of age or lack of care","answer" : "DILAPIDATED"},
{"question": "Including many different things : full of variety","answer" : "VARIEGATED"},
{"question": "Increased effectiveness that results when two or more people or businesses  work together","answer" : "SYNERGY"},
{"question": "Indefinite and very long period of time","answer" : "AEON"},
{"question": "Independent persons or a body officially appointed to settle a dispute","answer" : " Arbitrator"},
{"question": "Indirect and usually bad results of an action or event that may happen some  time afterwards","answer" : "Repercussion"},
{"question": "Influence or control over another country, a group of people","answer" : "Hegemony"},
{"question": "Influence or power , especially in politics or business","answer" : "Clout"},
{"question": "Informal ways of spreading information or rumors through conversation","answer" : " Grapevine"},
{"question": "Information about a person and about what they have done in their life","answer" : " Biodata"},
{"question": "Inscriptions on a building, statue, or coin","answer" : "Epigraph"},
{"question": "ill Institutions,places, or persons strongly maintaining particular principles,  attitudes, or activities","answer" : "Bastion"},
{"question": "Insulting remarks made in public","answer" : "Brickbats"},
{"question": "Intense military campaign intended to bring about a swift victory","answer" : "Blitzkrieg"},
{"question": "Introduction to a book or speech","answer" : "Preface"},
{"question": "Introduction to a book, play, etc.","answer" : "Prologue"},
{"question": "Involving a chance that something bad or unpleasant could happen","answer" : "Dicey"},
{"question": "Involving a lot of violence, confusion, or disorder","answer" : "Tumultuous"},
{"question": "Involving death or violence in a way that is strange, frightening, or unpleasant","answer" : " Macabre     "},
{"question": "Involving only one group or country","answer" : "Unilateral"},
{"question": "Items of additional material added at the end of a book or other publication","answer" : " Addendum    "},
{"question": "Japanese art of folding paper into shapes that look like birds, animals, etc.","answer" : " Origami"},
{"question": "Japanese flower arranging, that has strict formal rules","answer" : "Ikebana"},
{"question": "Japanese form of self defence and martial art that uses locks, holds, throws, and  the opponent's own movements","answer" : "Aikido"},
{"question": "Jargon or slang of a particular group or class","answer" : "Argot"},
{"question": "Jobs, activities, etc., that are very suitable for someone","answer" : "Niche"},
{"question": "Journals or newspapers, especially the official one of .an organization or  institution","answer" : "Gazette"},
{"question": "Journalists who are not on the regular staff of a newspaper but who write  stories for that newspaper","answer" : "Stringer"},
{"question": "Journeys especially by a group of people for a specific purpose","answer" : "Expedition    "},
{"question": "Killing (a person or animal) by squeezing the throat","answer" : "Strangle"},
{"question": "Killing (an animal) for food, kill (many people) in a very violent way","answer" : " Slaughter"},
{"question": "Killing (someone) illegally as punishment for a crime","answer" : "Lynch"},
{"question": "Killing of a large number of people","answer" : "Carnage"},
{"question": "Killing or wounding of people, typically on a large scale during a conflict","answer" : " Bloodshed"},
{"question": "Kindness shown to somebody when they are being punished : willingness not  somebody so severely","answer" : "Clemency"},
{"question": "Knowing everything : having unlimited understanding or knowledge","answer" : " omniscient"},
{"question": "Knowing or using several languages","answer" : "Polyglot            "},
{"question": "Lack of agreements between people, ideas, etc","answer" : "Discord     "},
{"question": "Lack of order : a confused or messy condition","answer" : "Disarray"},
{"question": "Lack of respect or dislike for someone or something","answer" : "Contempt"},
{"question": "Lack of seriousness","answer" : "Levity"},
{"question": "Lack of solidity or substance; thinness","answer" : "Tenuity"},
{"question": "Lack of the usual social or ethical standards in an individual or group","answer" : "Anomie  (anomy)"},
{"question": "Lacking confidence : not feeling comfortable around people, very careful about  acting or speaking","answer" : "Diffident"},
{"question": "(Land) used or suitable for growing crops","answer" : "Arable"},
{"question": "(Language) used in conversation but not in formal speech or writing","answer" : " Colloquial"},
{"question": "(Legislative body) having two chambers","answer" : "Bicameral"},
{"question": "Language of ordinary speechs rather than formal writing","answer" : "Vernacular"},
{"question": "Language or behaviour that is nonsense and is intended to hide the truth from  people","answer" : "Hocus-pocus"},
{"question": "Language that is intended to influence people and that may not be honest or  reasonable","answer" : "Rhetoric"},
{"question": "Language that is used among people who speak various different languages","answer" : " Lingua franca"},
{"question": "Language used by a particular group of people","answer" : "Parlance"},
{"question": "Language used for a particular activity or by a particular group of people","answer" : " Jargon"},
{"question": "Large amount of money that has been given to a school, hospital, etc., and that  is used to pay for its creation and continuing support : person's natural ability or  talent","answer" : "Endowment"},
{"question": "Large amount of rain that suddenly falls in an area : large amount of things that  come at the same time","answer" : "Deluge"},
{"question": "Large amount of something that is released suddenly","answer" : "Torrent"},
{"question": "Large and beautiful view of an area of land or Vista water   ","answer":"vista"},
{"question": "Large and very unpleasant amount of dirt","answer" : "Filth"},
{"question": "Large areas of land that have been farmed, too  much with the result that plants  will not grow there","answer" : "Badlands"},
{"question": "Large buildings or group of buildings for soldiers to live in","answer" : "Barracks"},
{"question": "Large ,burial ground, especially Qne not in a churchyard","answer" : "Cemetery"},
{"question": "Large business that is made of different. kinds of companies","answer" : "Conglomerate"},
{"question": "Large cages, buildings, or enclosures for keeping birds in","answer" : "Aviary"},
{"question": "Large group of people or things of a particular kind","answer" : "Bevy"},
{"question": "Large group of people, especially' an organized group with a particular purpose ","answer" : "Battalion"},
{"question": "Large group of people","answer" : "Throng"},
{"question": "Large notices or signs put up in a public place or carried by people","answer" : "Placard     "},
{"question": "Large number of things that appear or happen in a short period of time","answer" : "Spate"},
{"question": "Large open air fire used for burning rubbish or as part of a celebration","answer" : " Bonfire"},
{"question": "Large parties or celebrations","answer" : "Fete"},
{"question": "Large parties or celebrations","answer" : "Jamboree"},
{"question": "Large tents used for social or commercial functions . covered structures over  the entrance to a building","answer" : "Marquee"},
{"question": "Large calibre guns used in warfare on land","answer" : "Artillery"},
{"question": "Lasting for a very short time","answer" : "Evanescent"},
{"question": "Lasting for a very short time","answer" : "Ephemeral"},
{"question": "Late morning meals eaten instead of breakfast and lunch","answer" : "Brunch"},
{"question": "Laws or regulations made by a government","answer" : "Ordinance"},
{"question": "Laws or rules that limit or control something strong criticism","answer" : "Stricture"},
{"question": "Leaving (property) to a person or other beneficiary by a will","answer" : "Bequeath"},
{"question": "Legal agreements in which a person borrows money to buy property (such as a  house) and pays back the money over a period of years","answer" : "Mortgage"},
{"question": "Legal right to be the only one to reproduce, publish and sell a book, musical  recording, etc., for a certain period of time","answer" : "Copyright"},
{"question": "Letter or group of letters that is added at the beginning of a word to change its  meaning","answer" : "Prefix"},
{"question": "Level of respect that people have for a succesitful person, organizatum, etc","answer" : " Stature"},
{"question": "Light that is placed somewhere to guide vehicies and warn them of danger","answer" : " Beacon"},
{"question": "Likely to change in a very sudden or extreme way likely to become dangerous  or out of control","answer" : "Volatile"},
{"question": "Likely to have or produce good results","answer" : " Propitious"},
{"question": "Limited to a small number of people","answer" : "Esoteric"},
{"question": "Lines in a newspaper naming the writer of an article","answer" : "Byline"},
{"question": "Lines notionally drawn on the earth equidistant from the poles","answer" : "Equator"},
{"question": "Lines on a weather map that join places that have the same air pressure at a  particular time","answer" : "Isobar"},
{"question": "Lines on a weather map that join places that have the same temperature at a  particular time","answer" : "Isotherm"},
{"question": "Lines that have a series of short, sharp turns or angles","answer" : "Zigzag"},
{"question": "Lists of items required, things to be done, or points to be considered, used as a  reminder","answer" : "Checklist"},
{"question": "Lists of the books referred to in a scholarly work ,typically printed as an  appendix","answer" : "Bibliography"},
{"question": "Lists of the foods that may be ordered at a restaurant","answer" : "Menu     "},
{"question": "Lists of the people or things that belong to a particular group, team, etc.","answer" : " Roster"},
{"question": "Lists of the people who work for a company and the amount of money that the  company has agreed to pay them","answer" : "Payroll"},
{"question": "Lists that show who must do a certain job","answer" : "Rota"},
{"question": "Lively or energetic quality","answer" : "Vitality"},
{"question": "Living in trees","answer" : "Arboreal"},
{"question": "Long and angry fights or quarrels between two people or two groups","answer" : "Feud"},
{"question": "Long and angry speechs","answer" : "Tirade"},
{"question": "Long and complicated series of events","answer" : "Saga"},
{"question": "Long and determined efforts to achieve something that one believes to be right  or to stop something that one belives to be wrong","answer" : "Crusade"},
{"question": "Long journeys to a distant or unknown place especially over water or through  outer space","answer" : "voyage"},
{"question": "Long poems that tell the story of a hero's adventures","answer" : "epic"},
{"question": "Long speeches given by a character in a story, movie, play, etc., or by a  performer","answer" : "Monologue"},
{"question": "Long, complicated, and annoying process, descriptions","answer" : "Rigmarole"},
{"question": "Long, narrow boxes, typically of wood, in which a dead body is buried or  cremated","answer" : "COFFIN"},
{"question": "Long, thin sticks used by a magician or during magic tricks","answer" : "WAND"},
{"question": "Long, usually serious speeches that a character in a play make to an audience  and that reveal the character's thoughts","answer" : "SOLILOQUY"},
{"question": "Long-term security yielding a fixed rate of Debenture interest, issued by a  company and secured against assets","answer" : "DEBENTURE"},
{"question": "Looking at someone in an evil or unpleasantly Leer sexual way","answer" : "LEER"},
{"question": "Looking for private information about someone Snoop or something","answer" : "SNOOP"},
{"question": "Lots of energy and style","answer" : "Panache"},
{"question": "Loud and confused noises, strongly expressed Clamour protest or demand from  a large number of people","answer" : "CLAMOUR"},
{"question": "Loud, confusing mixture of noises that lasts for a Din long time","answer" : "DIN"},
{"question": "Loving and admiring oneself and especially one's Narcissism appearance too  much","answer" : "NARCISSISM             "},
{"question": "Made by combining different substances : not natural","answer" : "Synthetic"},
{"question": "Made or done without preparation","answer" : "Impromptu"},
{"question": "Made to be useful rather than to be decorative or comfortable","answer" : "Utilitarian     "},
{"question": "Made to look like an exact copy of something in order to trick people","answer" : " Counterfeit"},
{"question": "Made up of different things","answer" : "Sundry"},
{"question": "Made up of many different people or things","answer" : "Motley"},
{"question": "Made up of parts that are different","answer" : "Heterogeneous"},
{"question": "Magical liquid that can cure illness or extend life","answer" : "Elixir"},
{"question": "Main characters in a novel, play, movie, etc.","answer" : "Protagonist"},
{"question": "Main group of people in a Communistgovernment who make decisions about  policy","answer" : "Politburo"},
{"question": "Main or central part of a city or town","answer" : "Downtown"},
{"question": "Major changes or a period of change that causes a lot of conflict, confusion,  anger, etc.","answer" : "Upheaval"},
{"question": "Make (an idea, belief, etc.) known to many people","answer" : "Promulgate"},
{"question": "Making (someone or something) weaker or less effective usually in a secret or  gradual way","answer" : "Undermine"},
{"question": "Making (someone) feel or look young, healthy, or energetic again","answer" : "Rejuvenate"},
{"question": "Making (someone) want to know more about something","answer" : "Intrigue"},
{"question": "Making (something) as good or as effective as possible","answer" : "Optimize"},
{"question": "Men who want to marry a particular woman","answer" : "Suitor"},
{"question": "Managing or using money in a careful or wise way","answer" : "Thrifty"},
{"question": "Many changes or problems that happen over time","answer" : "Vicissitude"},
{"question": "Marks or qualities that shows what something is or what it could be","answer" : "Earmark"},
{"question": "Marks that are left on one's skin after a wound heals : feeling of great emotional  pain or sadness that is caused by a bad experience and that lasts for a long time ","answer" : "Scar"},
{"question": "Materials made of a network of wire or thread : Mesh complex or constricting  situation","answer" : "MESH"},
{"question": "Materials that are flowing out","answer" : "Efflux"},
{"question": "Meals consisting of several dishes from which guests serve themselves","answer" : "Buffet"},
{"question": "Meals to which everyone who is invited brings food to share","answer" : "Pot luck"},
{"question": "Measures designed merely to humour or placate someone","answer" : "Placebo"},
{"question": "Members of a group of people who move from place to place instead of living  in one place all the time","answer" : "Nomad"},
{"question": "Members of some religions (such as Christianity, Judaism, and Islam) who  deliver messages that are believed to have come from God","answer" : "Prophet"},
{"question": "Mental illness in which a person becomes very emotional or excited","answer" : "Mania"},
{"question": "Mental states in which one is confused and not able to think or speak clearly :  state of wild excitement and great happiness","answer" : "Delirium"},
{"question": "Metals made by combining two or more metallic elements","answer" : "Alloy"},
{"question": "Military groups controlling a governMENT AFTER taking control of it by  force","answer" : "GIMMICK     "},
{"question": "Money given as a reward","answer" : "BOUNTY"},
{"question": "Money or food given to poor people","answer" : "Alms"},
{"question": "Money or property that is given to you by somebody when they die","answer" : "Legacy"},
{"question": "Money that is less than the amount that is needed","answer" : "Deficit"},
{"question": "Money that is owed and should have been paid earlier","answer" : "Arrears"},
{"question": "Money that is paid in order to free someone who has been captured or  kidnapped","answer" : "Ransom"},
{"question": "Moral fables, especially one with animals as characters","answer" : "Apologue"},
{"question": "Morally good behavior or character","answer" : "VIRTUE"},
{"question": "Most important and basic facts or details about something","answer" : "NittY GittY"},
{"question": "Most important idea orparts of something","answer" : "Keynote"},
{"question": "Most important parts of something (such as a Most important parts of  something","answer" : "Crux"},
{"question": "Most successful or powerfull group of people","answer" : "Quintessence"},
{"question": "Moving about quickly from side to side or up and down","answer" : "Jiggle"},
{"question": "Movinig at a speed faster than walking by stepping with each front leg at the  same time as the opposite back leg","answer" : "Trot"},
{"question": "Moving or acting quickly to do, find, or get Scramble something often before  someone else does","answer" : "scramble"},
{"question": "Moving or acting too slowly","answer" : "Dawdle"},
{"question": "Move or lift (something) so that it is no longer","answer" : "Ruffle"},
{"question": "Moving quickly to one side in order to avoid being hit by (someone or  something)","answer" : "Dodge"},
{"question": "Moving to a new place","answer" : "Relocate"},
{"question": "Movements away from a place or situation especially because it is dangerous,  unpleasant, etc. : place that is quiet and private","answer" : "Retreat"},
{"question": "Movies about crime that uses dark shadows and lighting to show the  complicated moral nature of the subject","answer" : "Noir"},
{"question": "Mutual trust and friendship among people who spend a lot of time together","answer" : " Camaraderie"},
{"question": "Mysteries that can only be resolved by assembling various pieces of  information","answer" : "Jigsaw          "},
{"question": "Names that are wrong or not proper or appropriate","answer" : "Misnomer"},
{"question": "Names that someone (such as a writer) uses instead of his or her real name","answer" : " Pseudonym"},
{"question": "Narrow passageways between or behind building","answer" : "Alley"},
{"question": "Natural likings for and understanding of someone or something","answer" : "Affinity   "},
{"question": "New activities, projects, business, etc., that typically involve risk","answer" : "Venture"},
{"question": "New and experimental ideas and methods in art, music, or literature","answer" : "Avant-garde"},
{"question": "Newspapers with small pages (usually half the size of those in larger papers)","answer" : " Tabloid"},
{"question": "Newspapers that print a lot of shocking stories about people's private lives  rather than serious news","answer" : "Gutter press"},
{"question": "No longer active or effective : close to failure","answer" : "Moribund"},
{"question": "No longer existing or being used","answer" : "Defunct"},
{"question": "No longer used because something newer exists","answer" : "Obsolete"},
{"question": "Noisy and overexcited reactions or responses to something","answer" : "Brouhaha"},
{"question": "Noisy arguments or disagreements, especially in public","answer" : "Altercation"},
{"question": "Noisy arguments or fights","answer" : "Fracas"},
{"question": "Not able or willing to believe something","answer" : "Incredulous"},
{"question": "Not able to be corrected or changed","answer" : "Incorrigible"},
{"question": "Not able to be stopped or changed","answer" : "Inexorable"},
{"question": "Not able to communicate with other people","answer" : "Incommunicado"},
{"question": "Not acceptable to talk about or do","answer" : "Taboo"},
{"question": "Not active, not now developing or causing symptoms","answer" : "Quiescent"},
{"question": "Not as important as something else","answer" : "Subsidiary"},
{"question": "Not capable of life","answer" : "Inanimate"},
{"question": "Not clear in meaning : stated in a way that is general and not specific","answer" : "Vague"},
{"question": "Not completely clear or transparent but clear enough to allow light to pass  through","answer" : "Translucent"},
{"question": "Not connected with spiritual or religious matters","answer" : "Secular"},
{"question": "Not deserving serious attention","answer" : "Frivolous"},
{"question": "Not doing or involving much physical activities","answer" : "Sedentary"},
{"question": "Not easily described : having no special or interesting qualities, parts, etc. :  typical and uninteresting","answer" : "Nondescript"},
{"question": "Not easily stopped or pulled apart : very determined to do something","answer" : " Tenacious"},
{"question": "Not giving enough thought to other people's feelings or needs","answer" : "Inconsiderate"},
{"question": "Not having made a will","answer" : "Intestate"},
{"question": "Not having or showing good judgment","answer" : "Indiscreet"},
{"question": "Not having or showing good manners, good taste,or politeness","answer" : "Vulgar"},
{"question": "Not intended or planned","answer" : "Inadvertent"},
{"question": "Not interesting, funny, etc., because of being used too often","answer" : "Hackneyed"},
{"question": "Not keeping anything secret or hidden : honest and direct","answer" : "Upfront"},
{"question": "Not letting light through : not transparent, difficult to understand of explain","answer" : " Opaque"},
{"question": "Not liking to work or be active","answer" : "Indolent     "},
{"question": "Not lively or interesting : dull or boring","answer" : "Vapid"},
{"question": "Not made of physical substances : not able to be touched","answer" : "Intangible"},
{"question": "Not necessary or appropriate","answer" : "Unwarranted"},
{"question": "Not producing the desired effect","answer" : "Inefficacious"},
{"question": "Not showing enough care and attention","answer" : "Remiss"},
{"question": "Not strong or stable and likely to break","answer" : "Rickety"},
{"question": "Not very developed or advanced","answer" : "Rudimentary"},
{"question": "Not very easy to see or notice","answer" : "Inconspicuous"},
{"question": "Not willing to tell people about things","answer" : "Reticent"},
{"question": "Not within the range of what someone knows or understands","answer" : "Ken"},
{"question": "Novels, movies, etc., that are very exciting : a story full of exciting action,  mystery, adventure, or suspense","answer" : "Thriller"},
{"question": "Number of people who are killed or injured in an accident, disaster, war","answer" : "Toll    "},
{"question": "Objects (such as a ring or stone) that is believed to have magic powers and to  cause good things tohappen to the person who has it","answer" : "Talisman"},
{"question": "Objects or pictures used to suggest a thing that cannot be shown : person or  thing that represents an idea","answer" : "Emblem"},
{"question": "Object, pieces of evidence or some informations that help the police solve a  crime","answer" : "Clue"},
{"question": "Objects, activities, or ideas that are used as symbols of something else","answer" : " Metaphor"},
{"question": "Objects or materials that are collected because they are related to a particular  event, person, etc. : things collected as souvenirs","answer" : "Memorabilia"},
{"question": "Objects that are used to do a particular activity : objects of a particular kind","answer" : " Paraphernalia"},
{"question": "Occurring between members of the same country, group, or organization","answer" : " Internecine"},
{"question": "Of, belonging to, or seeming to come from an early time in the very ancient  past","answer" : "Primitive"},
{"question": "(Of a person) not identified by name; of unknown name","answer" : "Anonymous"},
{"question": "Offence of marrying someone while already married to another person","answer" : " Bigamy"},
{"question": "Official agreements that are made between two or more countries or groups","answer" : " Treaty"},
{"question": "Official announcements about a usually very important piece of news","answer" : " Communiqué"},
{"question": "Open opposition toward a person or group in authority","answer" : "Rebellion   "},
{"question": "Open to more than one interpretation : not having one obvious meaning","answer" : " Ambiguous"},
{"question": "Operations in which police or other forces surround a building and cut off  supplies, with the aim of forcing an armed person to surrender","answer" : "Siege"},
{"question": "Opinions or beliefs of the majority","answer" : "Vox populi"},
{"question": "Opponents or enemies that are very difficult to defeat","answer" : "Nemesis"},
{"question": "Opponents that are easy to defeat","answer" : "Pushover"},
{"question": "Orders that must be followed","answer" : "Diktat"},
{"question": "Organized search for a person and especially for a criminal","answer" : "Manhunt"},
{"question": "Original copies of a play, book, piece of music, etc., before those have been  printed","answer" : "Manuscript"},
{"question": "Ornaments or small pieces of jewellery thought to give protection against evil,  danger, or disease","answer" : "Amulet"},
{"question": "Out of control with anger or excitement; wild or frenzied","answer" : "Berserk"},
{"question": "Outdoor meals or parties when food is cooked in this way","answer" : "Barbecue"},
{"question": "Outlines or outer edges of something","answer" : "Contour"},
{"question": "Outside edges of an area : the area that surrounds a place or thing","answer" : "Periphery       "},
{"question": "Persons who are in charge of or takes care of something","answer" : "Warden"},
{"question": "Persons who are kept in a prison or mental hospital","answer" : "Inmate"},
{"question": "Persons who are killed or who suffer greatly for a religion, cause, etc.","answer" : "Martyr"},
{"question": "Persons who are not loyal to his or her own country, friends, etc.","answer" : "Traitor"},
{"question": "Persons who are not welcome or wanted in a place","answer" : "Intruder"},
{"question": "Persons who are running away to avoid being captured","answer" : "Fugitive"},
{"question": "Persons who are sent by one government to represent it in dealing with another  government","answer" : "Envoy"},
{"question": "Persons who are skilled in magic or who has magical powers : a sorcerer or a  magician, a person who is very good at something","answer" : "Wizard"},
{"question": "Persons who are unfairly blamed for something that others have done","answer" : " Scapegoat"},
{"question": "Persons who are very enthusiastic about something","answer" : "Fiend"},
{"question": "Persons who are walking in a city, along a road, etc.","answer" : "Pedestrian"},
{"question": "Persons who know a lot about something (such as art, wine, food, etc.) : an  expert in a particular subject","answer" : "Connoisseur"},
{"question": "Persons who lack experience and knowledge","answer" : "Greenhorn     "},
{"question": "Persons who leave onepolitical, religious, etc. group to join another that has  very different views : someone or something that causes trouble and cannot be  controlled","answer" : "Renegade"},
{"question": "Personswho like or admire women.","answer" : "Philogynist"},
{"question": "Persons who like seeing and talking or writing about something that is  considered to be private","answer" : "Voyeur"},
{"question": "Parts of checks, tickets, etc., that can be kept as a record when it is torn off","answer" : " Counterfoil"},
{"question": "Parts of cities in which members of a particular group or race live usually in  poor conditions","answer" : "Ghetto"},
{"question": "Parts of theatres, concert halls, etc. in which the audiences sit","answer" : "Auditorium"},
{"question": "Parts of the earth's surface that are directly above the place where an  earthquake starts","answer" : "Epicenter"},
{"question": "Parts of your mind that tell you whether your actions are right or wrong","answer" : " Conscience"},
{"question": "Parts or elements of something","answer" : "Facet"},
{"question": "Partial or total loss of memory","answer" : "Amnesia"},
{"question": "Partial refunds to someone who haspaid too much for tax, rent, or a utility","answer" : " Rebate"},
{"question": "Particular subjects or issues that are discussed often or repeatedly","answer" : "Theme"},
{"question": "Particular types or categories of literature or art","answer" : "Genre"},
{"question": "Particular ways of thinking : a person's attitude or set of opinions about  something","answer" : "Mindset"},
{"question": "Particular ways of walking","answer" : "Gait"},
{"question": "Passages between rows of seats in a building such as a church or theatre, an  aircraft, or train","answer" : "AISLE"},
{"question": "Paying money to get a publication or service regularly","answer" : "SUBSCRIBE"},
{"question": "People in the future","answer" : "POSTERITY"},
{"question": "People of high social status","answer" : "GENTRY"},
{"question": "People who are extremely poor","answer" : "DESTITUDE"},
{"question": "People who are famous, wealthy, and attractivi","answer" : "GLITTERATI"},
{"question": "People who can vote in an election","answer" : "ELECTORATE"},
{"question": "Performances of something","answer" : "RENDITION"},
{"question": "Periods immediately before an action or event","answer" : "RUN UP"},
{"question": "Periods of 1,000 years","answer" : "MILLENNIUM"},
{"question": "Periods of temporary economic decline during which trade and industrial  activities are reduced","answer" : "RECESSION"},
{"question": "Periods of time during which someone does not work at his or her regular job  and is able to rest, travel, do research, etc.","answer" : "SABBATICAL"},
{"question": "Periods of time that are very important in history","answer" : "EPOCH   "},
{"question": "Periods of time when people stay awake, especially at night, in order to watch a  sick person, say prayers, protest, etc","answer" : "VIGIL"},
{"question": "Periods of time when something (activities or programs) are stopped","answer" : " HIATUS"},
{"question": "Periods when days ending and nights beginning","answer" : "TWILIGHT"},
{"question": "Periods when many more babies are born than usual","answer" : "BABY BOOM"},
{"question": "Periods when something do not increase or advance any further","answer" : "PLATEAU"},
{"question": "PermAnent administrative offices departmeric;, especially governmental ones","answer" : " SECRETARIATE"},
{"question": "Persons or things regarded as an exact copy of another","answer" : "CLONE"},
{"question": "Persons or things that attract a lot of attention or interest","answer" : "CYNOSURE"},
{"question": "Persons or things that cause a change","answer" : "CATALYST"},
{"question": "Persons or things that do not go or move as quickly as others","answer" : "LAGGARD"},
{"question": "Persons or things that are connected with or related to another, often in a way  that one would not expect","answer" : "BEDFELLOW"},
{"question": "Persons or things that are extremely important or large in size","answer" : "COLOSSUS"},
{"question": "Persons or things that are the direct opposite of someone or something else","answer" : " ANTHITHESIS"},
{"question": "Persons or things that are the most important part of an organization, a plan,  etc, because everything else depends on them or it","answer" : "LINCHPIN"},
{"question": "Persons or things that one particularly dislike","answer" : "BETE NOIRE"},
{"question": "Persons or things that take the place of someone or something else","answer" : " SUBSTITUTE"},
{"question": "Persons or things that take the place or perform the duties of someone or  something else","answer" : "SURROGATE"},
{"question": "Persons or things which provide stability or confidence in an otherwise  uncertain situation","answer" : "ANCHOR"},
{"question": "Persons that somebody spend a lot of time with","answer" : "Crony"},
{"question": "Persons who accompany and look after another persons or group of people","answer" : " CHAPERONE"},
{"question": "Persons who actively oppose or are hostile to someone or something : an  adversary","answer" : "ANTAGONIST"},
{"question": "Persons who actively use the Internet especially in a proper and responsible  way","answer" : "NETIZEN         "},
{"question": "Qualities of always behaving in the same way or of having the same opinions,  standard, etc","answer" : "constituency   "},
{"question": "Qualities of being faithful to one's husband, wife, or sexual partner","answer" : "fidelity"},
{"question": "Qualities of being honest and fair","answer" : "integrity"},
{"question": "Qualities of being very similar or equal","answer" : "symmetry"},
{"question": "Qualities of being very unwilling to spend money","answer" : "parsimoney"},
{"question": "Qualities that causes people to feel sympathy and sadness","answer" : "pathos"},
{"question": "Qualities that makes one person or thing different from another","answer" : "trait"},
{"question": "Quantities of work that should have been done already, but has not yet been  done","answer" : "backlog"},
{"question": "Quick looks or glance","answer" : "dekko"},
{"question": "Quick series of soft, light sounds caused when things (such as leaves or pieces  ofpaper) rub against each other","answer" : "rustle"},
{"question": "Quiet and peaceful","answer" : "tranquil"},
{"question": "Quiet and polite, not showy or flashy","answer" : "demure"},
{"question": "Quotations from or references to a book, paper, or author, especially in a  scholarly work","answer" : "citation            "},
{"question": "(Route or journey) longer than the most direct way","answer" : "Circuitous"},
{"question": "Raised platforms for a speaker, performer, or the leader of an orchestra","answer" : " Podium"},
{"question": "Raised platforms in a large room or hall that people stand on when performing  or speaking to an audience","answer" : "Dais"},
{"question": "Range or series of related things","answer" : "Gamut"},
{"question": "Ready and excited to start to do something","answer" : "Raring"},
{"question": "Reasons or explanations for something","answer" : "Rationale"},
{"question": "Reasons that you give to hide your real reason for doing something","answer" : "Pretext"},
{"question": "Records of events year by year","answer" : "Annals"},
{"question": "Refers to the fact that something has been done or repeated so often that it has  become annoying or tiresome","answer" : "Ad nauseam"},
{"question": "Referring to sex in a rude but humorous way","answer" : "Ribald"},
{"question": "Refusing (something, such as an offer or suggestion) in a rude way","answer" : "Rebuff"},
{"question": "Refusing to be persuaded or to change one's mind","answer" : "Adamant"},
{"question": "Regular period of sleep or rest in the afternoon in some hot countries","answer" : "Siesta"},
{"question": "Regular, repeated patterns of sounds or movements","answer" : "Rhythm"},
{"question": "Reinforced underground shelters, typically for use in wartime","answer" : "Bunker"},
{"question": "Returning to an earlier and usually worse state or condition","answer" : "retograde"},
{"question": "Rich persons who have at least a million dollars, pounds","answer" : "millioniaries"},
{"question": "Rights or benefit that is given to some people and not to others","answer" : "priviledge"},
{"question": "Rights or the capacity to bring an action or to appear in a court","answer" : "local standi     "},
{"question": "Rights or privileges","answer" : "prerogative"},
{"question": "Rights to choose what should be done in a particular situation","answer" : "discretion"},
{"question": "Rights to vote in an election","answer" : "suffrage"},
{"question": "Ritual suicides by cutting open one's stomach with a sword","answer" : "hara-kiri"},
{"question": "Robots with a human appearance","answer" : "android"},
{"question": "Rooms in a public building where outdoor clothes or luggage may be left","answer" : " clockroom"},
{"question": "Rough or noisy","answer" : "rowdy"},
{"question": "Roughly made model of a person that is made in order to be damaged or  destroyed as a protest","answer" : "effigy"},
{"question": "Roughly orquickly thrust (a sharp or pointed object) someone or something","answer" : " jab"},
{"question": "Routine tasks, especially a household one","answer" : "chores"},
{"question": "Rules orprinciples that most people believe to be true","answer" : "axiom"},
{"question": "Rules that say how people should behave","answer" : "precept"},
{"question": "Rules about the proper and polite way to communicate with other people when  one is using the Internet","answer" : "netiquette       "},
{"question": "Sad moods or feelings","answer" : "melancholy"},
{"question": "Said to somebody who is leaving on a journey, to wish them a good journey","answer" : " bon vyoage"},
{"question": "Sailors who attacked ships at sea and stole from them : the person who acts in a  recklessly adventurous and often unscrupulous way, especially in business","answer" : " baccaneer"},
{"question": "Saying or writing very harsh and critical things about (someone or something)","answer" : " vilify"},
{"question": "Saying that (something) is smaller, less important, etc., than it really is","answer" : " understate"},
{"question": "Saying that something you said or wrote is not true or correct","answer" : "retract"},
{"question": "Saying that you are not responsible for (something) : to deny that you know  about or are involved in (something)","answer" : "disavow"},
{"question": "Scenes full of noise and confusion","answer" : "bedlam"},
{"question": "Searching for something especially by moving and looking through the  contents of a place","answer" : "rummage"},
{"question": "Searching through waste, junk, etc., for something that can be saved, used or  eaten","answer" : "scavenge"},
{"question": "Seats for passengers on a motorcycle","answer" : "pillion     "},
{"question": "Secret agreements especially in order to do something dishonest or to trick  people","answer" : "collusion"},
{"question": "Secret or disguised ways of writing : a code","answer" : "cipher"},
{"question": "Secretly try to ruin or destroy a government, political system, etc.","answer" : "subvert"},
{"question": "Sections or tables of subsidiary matter at the end of a book or document","answer" : " Appendix"},
{"question": "Seeming like real life because it is very clear, bright, or detailed, very bright in  color","answer" : "Vivid"},
{"question": "eeming to be seen everywhere","answer" : "Ubiquitous"},
{"question": "Selling (a business, property, etc.) especially to pay off debt","answer" : "Liquidate"},
{"question": "Sending (a person who has been accused of a crime) to another state or country  for trial","answer" : "Extradite"},
{"question": "Sending away (some of a company's work) to be done by people outside the  company","answer" : "Outsource"},
{"question": "Series of changes","answer" : "Flux"},
{"question": "Series of three novels, movies, etc., that are closely related and involve the  same characters or themes","answer" : "Trilogy"},
{"question": "Sets of clothes that are worn together : group of people working together in the  same activity","answer" : "Outfit"},
{"question": "Sets of ideas that somebody believes in and tries to persuade others to accept","answer" : " Gospel"},
{"question": "Sets of principles concerned with the nature and appreciation of beauty","answer" : " Aesthetics"},
{"question": "Sets of tools or supplies that a person uses for a particular purpose or activity","answer" : " Kit"},
{"question": "Severe mental orphysical pain or suffering","answer" : "Anguish"},
{"question": "Severe snowstorms with high winds : large quantity of things that may seem to  be attacking you","answer" : "Blizzard"},
{"question": "Sexually attracted to people of the same sex","answer" : "Homosexual"},
{"question": "Shared by, including or typical of a whole group of things : not specific","answer" : " Generic"},
{"question": "Shiny quality of a surface that refleqs light","answer" : "Luster"},
{"question": "Someone who predicts things that will happen in the future   ","answer":"Fortune teller"},
{"question": "Tending to be quiet : not speaking frequently","answer" : "Taciturn"},
{"question": "That can be done : that will be successful","answer" : "Viable"},
{"question": "The last of a series","answer" : "Omega"},
{"question": "The same book or piece of writing as the one that has just been mentioned","answer" : " Ibid"},
{"question": "The thing added to something else as a supplementary rather than an essential  part","answer" : "Adjunct"},
{"question": "The thing or a person that has no chance of success","answer" : "Noose"},
{"question": "The thing that existed before or logically precedes another","answer" : "Antecedent"},
{"question": "The thing that hides or covers somebody/something","answer" : "Cloak"},
{"question": "The thing that is added or attached to something larger or more important","answer" : " Appendage"},
{"question": "The thing that is inappropriate, especially a remark or expression","answer" : "Infelicity"},
{"question": "The thing that is most important to someone or something","answer" : "Raison detre"},
{"question": "The time at which something begins","answer" : "Inception"},
{"question": "The time that something of quality was produced","answer" : "Vintage"},
{"question": "The traditional knowledge, beliefs, and stories that relate to a particular place,  subject, or group","answer" : "Lore"},
{"question": "The treatment to improve the appearance and health of the feet or toenails","answer" : " Pedicure"},
{"question": "The trusted follower or supporter who performs unpleasant, wrong, or illegal  tasks for a powerful person","answer" : "Henchman"},
{"question": "The two-hundredth anniversary of a significant event","answer" : "Bicentenary     "},
{"question": "Theories or a group of ideas about how something should be done, made, or  thought about","answer" : "Paradigm    "},
{"question": "Unusual habits or way of behaving, something strange that happens by chance","answer" : " Quirk"},
{"question": "Unusual or excessive concern about one's health","answer" : "Hypochondria"},
{"question": "Unusual ways in which a particular person behaves or thinks","answer" : "Idiosyncrasy"},
{"question": "Urging or requesting (someone) solemnly or earnestly to do something","answer" : " Adjure"},
{"question": "Using (something) in a foolish or wasteful way","answer" : "Squander"},
{"question": "Use of deception or subterfuge to achieve one's purpose","answer" : "Chicanery"},
{"question": "Use of machines to do work that was previously done by people","answer" : "Automation"},
{"question": "Use of many words where fewer would do, especially in a deliberate attempt to  be vague or evasive","answer" : "Circumlocution"},
{"question": "Use of tricks especially to hide, avoid, or get something","answer" : "Subterfuge"},
{"question": "Use of words that mean the opposite of what one really wants to say especially  in order to insult someone, to show irritation, or to be funny","answer" : "Sarcasm"},
{"question": "Use of words to exchange thoughts and ideas","answer" : "Discourse"},
{"question": "Used in reference to luxurious accommodations","answer" : "Ritz"},
{"question": "Used to describe something that exists but that is not officially accepted or  recognized","answer" : "De facto"},
{"question": "Used to express excitement or joy","answer" : "Yahoo"},
{"question": "Used to express excitement when a discovery has been made","answer" : "Eureka"},
{"question": "Used to indicate that a named person is also known or more familiar under  another specified name","answer" : "Alias"},
{"question": "Used to refer to a process in which actors are chosen for a film/movie, etc. if  they have sex with the person in charge of choosing the artnrc","answer" : "Casting couch "},
{"question": "(Victory) won at too great a cost","answer" : "Pyrrhic"},
{"question": "Valuable stolen goods, especially those seized in war","answer" : "Booty"},
{"question": "Various forms in which the atoms of a chemical element can occur","answer" : "Isotope"},
{"question": "Very angry or violent disagreement between two or more people or groups","answer" : " Strife"},
{"question": "Very bad : causing great fear or worry","answer" : "Dire"},
{"question": "Very bad or frightening experience or situation","answer" : "Nightmare     "},
{"question": "Very big and powerful companies or organizations","answer" : "Behemoth"},
{"question": "Very careful about behaving properly and doing things in a correct and accurate  way","answer" : "Punctilious"},
{"question": "Very careful about doing something in an extremely accurate and exact way","answer" : " Meticulous"},
{"question": "Very close to being something without actually being it","answer" : "Virtual"},
{"question": "Very comfortable and expensive","answer" : "Opulent"},
{"question": "Very complicated and difficult to understand","answer" : "Turgid"},
{"question": "Very determined or loyal","answer" : "Diehard"},
{"question": "Very different, strange, or unusual","answer" : "Exotic"},
{"question": "Very dirty and unpleasant, immoral or dishonest","answer" : "Squalid"},
{"question": "Very dirty or untidy state or condition","answer" : "Mess"},
{"question": "Very eager or curious to hear or see something","answer" : "Agog"},
{"question": "Very excited or upset","answer" : "Overwrought"},
{"question": "Very famous or successful person","answer" : "Luminary    "},
{"question": "Ways of life, an attitude, an idea, etc. that has become very popular, system of  religious beliefs and rituals","answer" : "Cult"},
{"question": "Ways of protecting oneself against the loss of something","answer" : "Hedge"},
{"question": "Way that a person thinks about things","answer" : "Outlook"},
{"question": "Ways that a room or the inside of a building is decorated","answer" : "Decor"},
{"question": "Ways that prevents other people from finding out who you are","answer" : "Incognito"},
{"question": "Wealthy persons who give money and time to help make life better for other  people","answer" : "Philanthropist"},
{"question": "Well-known phrases that express a general truth about life or a rule about  behaviour","answer" : "Maxim"},
{"question": "Wild and drunken celebrations","answer" : "Bacchanal"},
{"question": "Wild and noisy celebrations","answer" : "Revelry"},
{"question": "Willing to do dishonest things in return for money","answer" : "Venal"},
{"question": "Wise, skilled, and respected government leaders","answer" : "Statesman"},
{"question": "Without a future date being arranged","answer" : "Sine die"},
{"question": "Women who control a family, group, or government","answer" : "Matriarch"},
{"question": "Women who have control or power over others","answer" : "Mistress"},
{"question": "Women who are paid to care for a young child usually in the child's home","answer" : " Nanny"},
{"question": "Women who are thought to have magic powers","answer" : "Witch"},
{"question": "Women who use their sexual charm to make men do what they wants","answer" : "Vamp"},
{"question": "Women who work in a bar, serving drinks","answer" : "Bartender     "},
{"question": "Women whose job are to be in charge of children or other women","answer" : "Matron       "},
{"question": "Young children who are just learning to walk","answer" : "toddler"},
{"question": "Young women who is not married","answer" : "damsel"},
{"question": "Young Person who are usually talented in some way","answer" : "prodigy"},
{"question": "Young person who are taught and helped by someone who has a lot of  knowledge and experience","answer" : "protege"}]               